<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Waterfalls in karnataka</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    
    <string name="name1h">name1h</string>
<string name="name2h">name2h</string>
<string name="name3h">name3h</string>
<string name="name4h">name4h</string>
<string name="name5h">name5h</string>
<string name="name6h">name6h</string>
<string name="name7h">name7h</string>
<string name="name8h">name8h</string>
<string name="name9h">name9h</string>
<string name="name10h">name10h</string>
<string name="name11h">name11h</string>
<string name="name12h">name12h</string>
<string name="name13h">name13h</string>
<string name="name14h">name14h</string>
<string name="name15h">name15h</string>
<string name="name16h">name16h</string>
<string name="name17h">name17h</string>
<string name="name18h">name18h</string>
<string name="name19h">name19h</string>
<string name="name20h">name20h</string>
<string name="name21h">name21h</string>
<string name="name22h">name22h</string>
<string name="name23h">name23h</string>
<string name="name24h">name24h</string>
<string name="name25h">name25h</string>
<string name="name26h">name26h</string>
<string name="name27h">name27h</string>
<string name="name28h">name28h</string>
<string name="name29h">name29h</string>
<string name="name30h">name30h</string>



    <string name="falls1">name1</string>
    <string name="falls2">name2</string>
    <string name="falls3">name3</string>
    <string name="falls4">name4</string>
    <string name="falls5">name5</string>
    <string name="falls6">name6</string>
    <string name="falls7">name7</string>
    <string name="falls8">name8</string>
    <string name="falls9">name9</string>
    <string name="falls10">name10</string>
    <string name="falls11">name11</string>
    <string name="falls12">name12</string>
    <string name="falls13">name13</string>
    <string name="falls14">name14</string>
    <string name="falls15">name15</string>
    <string name="falls16">name16</string>
    <string name="falls17">name17</string>
    <string name="falls18">name18</string>
    <string name="falls19">name19</string>
    <string name="falls20">name20</string>
    <string name="falls21">name21</string>
    <string name="falls22">name22</string>
    <string name="falls23">name23</string>
    <string name="falls24">name24</string>
    <string name="falls25">name25</string>
    <string name="falls26">name26</string>
    <string name="falls27">name27</string>
    <string name="falls28">name28</string>
    <string name="falls29">name29</string>
    <string name="falls30">name30</string>
    <string name="icon1">icon1</string>
    <string name="icon2">icon2</string>
    <string name="icon3">icon3</string>
    <string name="icon4">icon4</string>
    <string name="icon5">icon5</string>
    <string name="icon6">icon6</string>
    <string name="icon7">icon7</string>
    <string name="icon8">icon8</string>
    <string name="icon9">icon9</string>
    <string name="icon10">icon10</string>
    <string name="icon11">icon11</string>
    <string name="icon12">icon12</string>
    <string name="icon13">icon13</string>
    <string name="icon14">icon14</string>
    <string name="icon15">icon15</string>
    <string name="icon16">name16</string>
    <string name="icon17">icon17</string>
    <string name="icon18">icon18</string>
    <string name="icon19">icon19</string>
    <string name="icon20">icon20</string>
    <string name="icon21">icon21</string>
    <string name="icon22">icon22</string>
    <string name="icon23">icon23</string>
    <string name="icon24">icon24</string>
    <string name="icon25">icon25</string>
    <string name="icon26">icon26</string>
    <string name="icon27">icon27</string>
    <string name="icon28">icon28</string>
    <string name="icon29">icon29</string>
    <string name="icon30">icon30</string>
    <string name="name1">Jog Falls</string>
    <string name="name2">Dudhsagar Falls</string>
    <string name="name3">Abbey Falls</string>
    <string name="name4">Irpu Falls</string>
    <string name="name5">Unchalli Falls</string>
    <string name="name6">Hebbe Falls</string>
    <string name="name7">Gokak Falls</string>
    <string name="name8">Chunchunkatte Falls</string>
    <string name="name9">Barkana Falls</string>
    <string name="name10">Mekedatu</string>
    <string name="name11">Gaganachukki Falls</string>
    <string name="name12">Bharachukki Falls</string>
    <string name="name13">Kunchikal Falls</string>
    <string name="name14">Varapoha Falls</string>
    <string name="name15">Magod Falls</string>
    <string name="name16">Mallalli Falls</string>
    <string name="name17">Alekan Falls</string>
    <string name="name18">Bandaje Falls</string>
    <string name="name19">Dondole Falls</string>
    <string name="name20">Hebbe falls</string>
    <string name="name21">Kalahatti Falls</string>
    <string name="name22">Lalguli Falls</string>
    <string name="name23">Sathodi Falls </string>
    <string name="name24">Shivgange Falls</string>
    <string name="name25">Sirimane Falls </string>
    <string name="name26">Devaragundi Falls</string>
    <string name="name27">Godchinamalki Falls</string>
    <string name="name28">Hanumanagundi Falls</string>
    <string name="name29">Muthyalamaduvu Falls</string>
    <string name="name30">Balamuri Falls</string>
    <string name="title_activity_falls_details">FallsDetails</string>
    <string name="info1">Jog Falls is created by the Sharavathi River falling from a height of 253 m (830 ft), It 30km from Sagara taluk,shimoga district,Karnataka, India</string>
    <string name="info2">Dudhsagar Falls (literally Sea of Milk ) is a tiered waterfall located on the Mandovi River with Karnataka state,Total height-310 metres (1017 feet),It is 60 km from Panaji city(goa state capital) by road and 46 km from Madgaon railway junction by train</string>
    <string name="info3">Abbey Falls (also spelled Abbi Falls  and Abbe Falls)  is in Kodagu, in the Western  Ghats in Karnataka, India. It is  located 8 km from the town of  Madikeri and 268 km from Bangalore.</string>
    <string name="info4">The Irupu Falls  are located in the Brahmagiri Range in the Kodagu district of Karnataka, India, bordering the Wayanad district of Kerala. "Height: 52m", Irupu is situated at 48 km from Virajpet, 260 km from Bangalore and 120 km from Mysore. The Falls can be visited by the highway from Gonikopal to Nagerhole National Park off the Kutta Road after Srimangala. </string>
    <string name="info5"> Unchalli Falls, is a waterfall created by a 116 metres (381 ft) drop in the Aghanashini river. The fall is located in Siddapura, Uttara Kannada District of Karnataka, India. </string>
    <string name="info6">Hebbe Falls  are situated at  about 10 km away from the famous hill station  Kemmangundi in Karnataka, India.  This waterfalls are inside a coffee  estate and can be reached either by  walk or four-wheeler. Hebbe Falls  gushes down from a height of 551 ft</string>
    <string name="info7">The Gokak Falls located on the Ghataprabha river in Belgaum district of Karnataka, India. The waterfall is six kilometers away from Gokak, a nearby town.
July to September is the best season to visit the place.</string>
    <string name="info8">Chunchanakatte Falls is a waterfall on the Kaveri River, near the village of Chunchanakatte inkrishnarajanagar taluk of Mysore district, Karnataka, India. Water cascades from a height of about 20 meters, It is located at approximately 15 km from the town of KR Nagar.</string>
    <string name="info9">The Barkana Falls are among the ten highest waterfalls in India. They are located near Agumbe in Shimoga district ofstate of Karnataka. The Barkana falls are formed by the Sita river. Total height  - 850 feet /259 meters</string>
    <string name="info10">Mekedatu is a location along Kaveri in Kanakapura Taluk. Sangama is the place where Arkavati merges with Kaveri.From this point, about 3.5 kilometers downstream, the river Kaveri flows through a deep gorge so narrow that one would think that a goat can leap across it , It is about 100 km from Bangalore via Kanakapura</string>
    <string name="info11">the right segment of shivanasamudra waterfalls  is called barachukki , location-85 kms from Mysore and 139 kms from Bangalore, Shivanasamudra  is a small town in the Mandya District of the state of Karnataka, India. It is situated on the banks of the river Kaveri</string>
    <string name="info12">the left segment of shivanasamudra waterfalls  is called Gaganachukki, Height: 98 m, Flow rate: 934 m³/s, location-85 kms from Mysore and 139 kms from Bangalore, Shivanasamudra  is a small town in the Mandya District of the state of Karnataka, India. It is situated on the banks of the river Kaveri</string>
    <string name="info13">Kunchikal Falls is also called Kunchikal Abbe, are located near Masthikatte-Hulikal in Udupi-Shimoga district border of state of Karnataka. Kunchikal falls are formed by Varahi river. Varahi River cascades down hundreds of rocks near Hulikal (Ghati Temple), Hosanagara taluk, Shimoga District, Kunchikal falls cascades down rocky boulders and total height of this fall is 455 meters (1,493 feet) and this height makes this falls as highest waterfalls of India. The total length of cascade exceeds 1 km.</string>
    <string name="info14">Vajrapoha Falls :Vajrapoha Falls (also Vajrapoya waterfalls), a waterfall in the Belgaum district of Karnataka in South West India, is situated about in the mountainous forest 4 kilometres (2.5 mi) from the village of Jamboti. Between the village of Gavali and Chapoli on an elevated hillock, the Mandovi River that flows to the beautiful Vajrapoha Falls that fall for up to 200 metres (660 ft) and are best seen after the mansoon season (June-October). The falls are about 1.5 hours southwest of Belgaum</string>
    <string name="info15">Magod Falls is a waterfall in Uttara Kannada district of Karnataka. The waterfall lies deep in forest. The river Betdi(also called as Gangavalli) makes a 198m leap forming the Magod Falls. The falls goes dry during the summer months and misty during the monsoon season. There is a large lake on the way to Magod Falls known as Kavadikere.</string>
    <string name="info16">mallalli falls The falls is formed from KUMARADHARA River passing by. Falls has a height of about 62m, Mallali falls is almost 28 kms from somwarpet panchayat town in Kodagu district</string>
    <string name="info17">Alekan falls is about 18 km from Charmadi in Charmadi Ghats. Alekan falls is situated on the way to "Kottigehara" from Charmadi. This place is just next to the road before 4 km from Kottigehara, This water falls is just next to a small bus stop by name "alekan horatti".</string>
    <string name="info18">Bandaje falls is a waterfall located in the Charmadi ghat section of the Western Ghats in the Belthangady taluk of Dakshina Kannada district, Karnataka.
it flows as a single stream, and falls from approximately 400+ metres in between the vallies of Western Ghat. This flows further and joins the river Netravathi as a tributary</string>
    <string name="info19">Dondole Waterfalls is a beautiful waterfall in Belthangady taluk of Dakshina Kannada district, The Dondole Falls is located at a distance of 20 km from a place called "Kakkinje", which is just 3 Km before Charmadi on Ujire-Charmadi road.</string>
    <string name="info20">Hebbe Falls are situated at about 10 km away from the famous hill station Kemmangundi in Karnataka, India. This waterfalls are inside a coffee estate and can be reached either by walk or four-wheeler.  Address: Kesavinamane, Height: 168 m</string>
    <string name="info21">Kalhatti Falls or Kalahasti Falls is located at Kallattipura in Chikmagalur district of Karnataka. The waterfall is only 10 kilometers away from Kemmangundi hill station. It offers an excellent view of the cascading water from the Chandra Drona Hill from 122 meters (400 ft) above in front of the Veerabhadreshwara Temple dedicated to Lord Shiva.</string>
    <string name="info22">Lalguli Falls of Karnataka is just 15 kilometers away from Yellapur in Uttar Kannad District. Bangalore is 535 kilometers away from Lalguli Falls. The very famous waterfall is besieged by the plush greenery, rocky hills and various wildlife, It is created by River Kali when it rolls down the rocky steps from a height of around 250 feet in a series of picturesque rapids of the set at different heights from 61 m to 91 m. The scene of the water showering from the great height is amazing and fills you up with dismay.</string>
    <string name="info23">Satoddi Falls is a waterfall in India that is formed by several unnamed streams near Kallaramarane Ghat, Uttara Kannada District, near Sirsi, and 32 km from Yellapur. It is about 15 metres (49.2 feet) tall. The stream then flows into the backwaters of the Kodasalli Dam, into the Kali River.</string>
    <string name="info24">The Shivaganga falls is a 74 m high waterfall on the river Sonda in Uttara Kannada, India. This is about 22 km away from the town of Sirsi. The waterfall is located in an area of thick forest.</string>
    <string name="info25">Sirimane Falls is located at a distance of 5 km from Kigga near Sringeri, a popular pilgrim center. Nearest Airport is Mangalore and nearest Railway stations are udupi (96 KM) and shimoga (114 KM).</string>
    <string name="info26">Devaragundi meaning "Rockhole of God", is a waterfall in India. It is created by one of the mountain streams at Thodikana, Thodikana is an Indian village nestled in the foothills of the Western Ghats in southern Karnataka. It is a beautiful little village in Sullia taluk of Dakshina Kannada district, about 100 km from Mangalore city.This village is full of greenary and very nice place to visit,devaragundi waterfalls can be reached by going further for about 1.5 kilometres from Sri Mallikarjuna Temple towards the Patti Hills. One must cross two streams, climb uphill, and walk through a private arecanut farm to view this magnificent waterfall. It is cautioned that no one should step into the water in the surrounding of the waterfall, as its depth is unknown.</string>
    <string name="info27">The Godachinmalki Falls is a waterfall located on Markandeya river in Belgaum district, Gokak Taluk, Karnataka, India. It is 15 kilometers away from Gokak and 40 kilometers from Belgaum. It is located in a deep green valley, Godachinmalki falls, also known as Markandeya falls, is located in a rugged valley, which is approachable from Godachinamalaki village by walking as well as by vehicle through an irregular forest route for about 2 kilometers and there are two routes to rech falls from Godachinamalki, one is vai Malebail road by crossing bridge at godachinamalki and another one is vai Gurusiddeshwar Temple(Hatti Siddeshwar). It can also be reached from Nirvaneshwara Matha near Yogikolla, only by foot, To reach Godachinamalki Falls from Belgaum vai Ankalagi, Pachhapur and Mavanur, frequent bus facility is available from Belgaum and Gokak and nearest railway station is Pachhapur, which is about 8 kilometers and good train facility is available from Belgaum to Miraj, all most all trains stops in Pachhapur railway station, There are actually two falls formed here. The Markandeya river takes a first fall from a height of about 25 metres and flows into a rocky valley. After a short distance from the rocky valley, it takes the second fall from a height of about 20 metres.</string>
    <string name="info28">Hanumanagundi Falls or Suthanabbe Fallsis located in the hilly surroundings of the Kudremukh National Park in the Chikkamagaluru district of Karnataka, India, Suthanabbe Falls is located between Karkala and Lakya dam in the Kudremukh national park. The water falls from a height of 22 meters creating a scenic surroundings around it.</string>
    <string name="info29">Muthyalamaduvu,also known as Pearl Valley,It is near a town called Anekal on the outskirts of Bangalore. It may be easier and faster to reach this town via Hosur Road, although there is another route via Bannerghatta National Park, It is a popular picnic spot situated about 45km south of Bangalore in Karnataka. The Muthyalamaduvu Falls or the Pearl Valley Falls is a gushing stream cascading down from a height of 92 m. The drops of water strewn across the rock surface on impact lend the appearance of scattered pearls. Hence the name. The fall, its sereneambience and the lush green valley is a huge draw for visitors. </string>
    <string name="info30">Balmuri and Edmuri waterfalls are two small beautiful waterfalls, located 3 kms off the Mysore to the KRS (Krishna Raja Sagara) main road. The place where the Balmuri and Edmuri waterfalls are located is surrounded by lush greenery and is a hot spot among the locals as well. A visit to this place is calming and relaxing.
Technically, Balmuri and Edmuri waterfalls are not actually waterfalls. It is mostly flowing water of the Kaveri. At a particular spot in the Balmuri, there is step of about 6 feet from which creates the effect of a mini-waterfall....  Distance based on areas :- "15km from srirangapatna ","38 km from mandya district","16 km from mysore city","3 km from krs dam"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_full_screen">FullScreen</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>